Contact

XOM.ALBUKHORI@GMAIL.COM

www.linkedin.com/in/asbukhori (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Kotlin

Laravel

Project Estimation

Languages

English

Indonesian

Abdush Shomad Bukhori

Fullstack Software Engineer | Website & Mobile App East Java

Summary

I am an IT professional with 4+ years of experience in developing web or mobile based applications. Think critically in solving problems effectively and efficiently. Have good communication skills and love to discuss about the issues in application development.

The scope of applications that I have developed include Hospitality, Healthcare, E-Commerce, Onlineshop, Company Profile, Games, E-Vote, Personal Blog and Fintech.

The Featured Technology Stack that I use include Codeigniter Framework, Golang, ReactJS, Flutter, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase.

Experience

PT Mamalyfe Selalu Diberkati Acting Head of IT Department June 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Surabaya, East Java, Indonesia

- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve business objectives
- Collaborate with the Sales Marketing team to help with the sales process
- Communicate professionally with vendors, IT team, Customer Service team, designer team, content creator team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in applications both backend, frontend, database and server
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Database & Workflow related to developed features
- Guiding the team in developing features according to the design that has been made
- Coding and Testing both Backend (API, Third party Integration) and Frontend (Assist Team when needed)

PT Alfath Technologi Kreatif
IT Project Manager
March 2019 - April 2021 (2 years 2 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

- Create Application required by company and client
- Maintaining the Application that has been created in accordance with the cooperation agreement with the client
- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve application development goals by company and client
- Communicate professionally with IT team, Customer Service team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in the company's own app
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Workflow related to developed features
- Guiding the team in developing features according to the design that has been made
- Coding and Testing both Backend and Frontend

Kelola.net

IT Manager

August 2018 - April 2021 (2 years 9 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

- Create Web Application required by the company
- Maintaining the Web Application that has been created
- Provide consultation and strategic advice to achieve business objectives
- Collaborate with the Sales Marketing team to help with the sales process
- Communicate professionally with IT team, Customer Service team, designer team, content creator team, and management
- Troubleshoot issues that come out in applications both backend, frontend, database and server
- Analyze business requirements and provide estimates of work required
- Create Concepts/Ideas to be implemented in Applications
- Scheduling work time related to application features that are developed
- Designing Database & Workflow related to developed features
- Coding and Testing both Backend and Frontend
- Do Online and Offline Training Sessions regarding the Use of Applications for users

Syariahrooms Hospitality Software Developer October 2017 - July 2018 (10 months)

Malang, East Java, Indonesia

- Create information systems required by the company
- Maintaining the Information System that has been created
- Create features required by the company

Education

Universitas Islam Negeri Maulana Malik Ibrahim Bachelor's degree, Informatics Engineering · (July 2015 - November 2021)

Madrasah Aliyah Negeri 2 Gresik Student, Science · (2012 - 2015)